



Biluta Titus

• Home: str. Lapusului nr.15, 400171, CluiNapoca, Romania

Email: titusbiluta@gmail.com Phone: (+40) 753404949

Website: https://titusbilutaviorel.github.io/CV/

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/titus-biluta-478337274/

(instagram: titus.biluta

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 07/02/1999 **Nationality:** Romanian

ABOUT ME

Currently, I am a master's degree student at Technical University of Cluj-Napoca specializing in advanced manufacturing process control engineering, Faculty of Automation.

Alongside my academic pursuits, I devote my free time to sports, engaging in both fitness and basketball.

I believe that perseverance and a passion for technology guide me in my academic and personal journey. Also, I have a passion for design and simulation, which emerged when I realized that it is a way to create something both aesthetically and functionally at the same time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[2017 - 2018] **Service IT**

Virtual Reality Cluj

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania PC assembly

maintenance of computers

[2020 - 2021]

Internship at college - Security Systems Engineer

Saico General Cables

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

$[\ 2021\ -\ 2022\]$ CFR Anti-Doping Assistant - UEFA Conference League

National Anti-Doping Agency (ANAD)

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[2022 - Current]

Master's student in Computer Science and Automation (ICAF).

Technical University Of Cluj-Napoca https://ac.utcluj.ro/acasa.html

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania



[2018 - 2022]

Engineer (Electrical Engineering)

Technical University Of Cluj-Napoca https://ie.utcluj.ro/acasa.html

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

[2014 – 2018] High school student

"Onisifor Ghibu" Theoretical High School https://www.liceul-onisifor-ghibu.ro/

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): romana Other language(s): English

DIGITAL SKILLS -

Web design

CSS Grid | Basic Docker knowledge | ¡Query library | CSS Flexbox | HTML, CSS, lavascript

PC Office

Microsoft Excel | Microsoft PowerPoint | Microsoft Office | Social Media | Microsoft

Electric

Ansys Q2D/Maxwell/HFSS | MATLAB-Simulink | OrCAD-PSPICE

IDE - IntelliJ, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code | Git, GitHub, GitLab

Other

SolidWorks | mathematical programming language: Matlab, MathCad

PROJECTS

LED Resonance - Arcade Game (Bachelor's Thesis)

Throughout the course of a game, in order to have greater power to destroy an enemy, more intense vibrations are needed. Vibrations are obtained through high resonances.

When a physical system is subjected to a successive external action, with a frequency close to its own, a vibration state called resonance is formed.

To highlight this resonance, a circuit consisting of an LED strip and an accelerometer/ gyroscope is chosen. The resonance is visible only when the module with accelerometer and gyroscope is activated by a sudden left-right movement.

The game reproduced by me, one-dimensional, consists of a breadboard, a Wi-Fi module (ESP32), another module consisting of the gyroscope and accelerometer (MPU6050), wires, a buzzer connected to an audio amplifier (PAM8043), a 470 Ohm resistor, a power supply module, and a LED strip with 144 diodes (NEOPIXEL).

The gyroscope and accelerometer have the role of helping the LED strip to know how the MPU6050 component is oriented and to understand its position in order to display the green LED. The precision of these functions in the module is very high.

Link: https://flic.kr/p/2pz3iZa



Frontend - Glas

The project was created using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and represents the web application for the clothing brand that I plan to launch in the future.

Link: https://titusbilutaviorel.github.io/Glas/

SolidWorks - Lighter

An assembly (lighter) made up of eight components fully defined.

Link: https://flic.kr/p/2pz3nAP

SolidWorks - Bike

An assembly (bicycle) made up of nine components fully defined.

Link: https://flic.kr/p/2pu4YrG